[
  {
    "itemName": "wq_number",
    "roiFront": "569,13,50,32",
    "roiBack": "569,13,50,32",
    "mode": "Digit",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "挑戰券的數量"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_wanted",
    "roiFront": "9,145,123,381",
    "roiBack": "9,145,123,381",
    "mode": "Full",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "懸賞封印"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_text_1",
    "roiFront": "18,232,101,33",
    "roiBack": "18,232,101,33",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "懸.*印",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_text_2",
    "roiFront": "19,377,99,32",
    "roiBack": "19,377,99,32",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "懸.*印",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_num_1",
    "roiFront": "41,260,54,27",
    "roiBack": "41,260,54,27",
    "mode": "DigitCounter",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_num_2",
    "roiFront": "39,406,56,26",
    "roiBack": "39,406,56,26",
    "mode": "DigitCounter",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_num_unknown_1",
    "roiFront": "32,260,72,27",
    "roiBack": "32,260,72,27",
    "mode": "Digit",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "备用识别1"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_num_unknown_2",
    "roiFront": "34,406,65,24",
    "roiBack": "34,406,65,24",
    "mode": "Digit",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "备用识别2"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_type_1",
    "roiFront": "544,238,55,36",
    "roiBack": "544,238,55,36",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_type_2",
    "roiFront": "544,311,55,30",
    "roiBack": "544,311,55,30",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_type_3",
    "roiFront": "544,382,54,30",
    "roiBack": "544,382,54,30",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_type_4",
    "roiFront": "545,452,52,32",
    "roiBack": "545,452,52,32",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_info_1",
    "roiFront": "609,236,309,45",
    "roiBack": "609,236,309,45",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_info_2",
    "roiFront": "612,308,298,41",
    "roiBack": "612,308,298,41",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_info_3",
    "roiFront": "612,376,305,44",
    "roiBack": "612,376,305,44",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_info_4",
    "roiFront": "613,446,315,44",
    "roiBack": "613,446,315,44",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_monster_type",
    "roiFront": "165,215,45,175",
    "roiBack": "165,215,45,175",
    "mode": "Full",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "怪物名称,如酒吞，阎魔等"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_text_all",
    "roiFront": "20,140,110,390",
    "roiBack": "20,140,110,390",
    "mode": "Full",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": ""
  }
]